we've been given
two local variables first name and
last name and we've been instructed to
combine these two names together to form
a full name
and assign that value to a variable
named full name
then we're going to print the value of
full name
there's more than one way that we can
combine the values of these two
variables
let's begin by concatenating them
together
we'll pass full name to put us
and output its value
you can see that we've successfully
combined the first name and last name
but we forgot an important detail
we want a space between our first name
and last name
so we'll concatenate that space between
the values of first name and last name
and now our output matches the example
output
important to note that concatenation
returns a new string
rather than mutating its color
we've stored this new string in the
variable full name
alternatively we could use string
interpolation here
using double quotes and the octothorpe
and curly brace syntax of
interpolation
we've combined the first name and
lastname variables into a string